<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-05-01T19:17:50+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">A journey in and out</title><subtitle>About life, road and tech</subtitle><author><name>ilhan</name></author><entry><title type="html">Notes-2: English study about describing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/study%20notes/Notes-2-English/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Notes-2: English study about describing" /><published>2022-03-12T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-03-12T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/study%20notes/Notes-2-English</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/study%20notes/Notes-2-English/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) Notes-2: English study about describing</p>

<h3 id="words">Words</h3>
<ul>
  <li><strong>catchy</strong> : memorable</li>
  <li><strong>commercial</strong> : converned with or engaged in commerce</li>
  <li><strong>disturbing</strong> : causing anxiety; worrying</li>
  <li><strong>dull</strong> : lacking interest or exciment</li>
  <li><strong>gripping</strong> : firmly holding the attention or interest; exciting</li>
  <li><strong>hilarious</strong> : extremely amuzing</li>
  <li><strong>over-the-top</strong> : to an excessive or exaggerated degree</li>
  <li><strong>uplifting</strong> : inspiring happiness, optimism or hope</li>
  <li><strong>weird</strong> : uncanny</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="sentences">Sentences</h3>
<ul>
  <li>It didn’t do much for me. It’s very commercial.</li>
  <li>It is just too much for my liking, really over-the-top.</li>
  <li>It does nothing for me. It’s quite boring, quite dull.</li>
  <li>A: What kind of thing do you do in your free time?</li>
  <li>B: I guess the films are the main thing.</li>
  <li>A: Really. Do you go cinema much then?</li>
  <li>Yeah. I mean it depend’s what’s on.</li>
  <li>I’m happy just to watch at home.</li>
  <li>Don’t you want to see it on the big screen?</li>
  <li>To be honest, I am not that keen on action movies.</li>
  <li>I suppose, I’d rather see other things.</li>
  <li>It was so over-the-top. That scene where he eats the live octopus! It was all a bit too weird for my liking.</li>
  <li>C: As I said, it is not really my kind of thing. So what other films are you into?</li>
  <li>D: Oh all sorts. (every type!)</li>
  <li>I’m really into action movies.</li>
  <li>I’ve heard it is good. I was actually thinking of going to see it.</li>
  <li>I thought it was supposed to be a feel-good movie.</li>
  <li>What did they think of them?</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="disaggrements">Disaggrements</h3>
<ul>
  <li>I guess but <strong>to be honest I’m not that keen on</strong> action movies.</li>
  <li>It was all <strong>a bit too</strong> weird <strong>for my liking.</strong></li>
  <li>As I say, it’s <strong>not really my kind of thing.</strong></li>
  <li>It was not bad, <strong>I suppose but ..</strong></li>
</ul>

<p>We often soften responses by using phrases such as <strong>I’m not that keen on, I guess, I suppose, to be honest, for my liking..</strong> We also use <strong>a bit</strong> to soften negative adjectives.</p>

<h3 id="quotes-about-art">Quotes about art</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Art is the lie that enables us to realise the truth.</li>
  <li>Art is what you can get away with.</li>
  <li>The urge of destroy is also a creative urge.(<em>urge: impulse, desire</em>)</li>
  <li>The more minimal the art, the longer the explanation.</li>
  <li>Art never responds to the wish to make it democratic; it is not for everybody; it is only for those who are willing to undergo the effort needed to understand it.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="descriptive-sentences">Descriptive sentences</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Bold colours are very bright, strong and clear, whereas subtle colours are not strong or bright. They’re softer and more delicate.</li>
  <li>delicate: (fine, elegant) very fine in texture or structure, of intricate workmanship or quality. Ex: A spider’s web is stong yet delicate</li>
  <li>subtle: (fine-drawn, ultra-fine, elusive) so delicate or precise as to be difficult to analyze or describe. Ex: His language expresses rich and subtle meanings.</li>
  <li>If a painting is <strong>conventional</strong>, it’s traditional and not new or different in any way.</li>
  <li>conventional: based on or in accordance with what is generally done or believed.</li>
  <li>If it’s <strong>atmospheric</strong>, a painting creates a special mood - such as a feeling of romance or mystery.</li>
  <li>If it’s <strong>ambiguous</strong>, the meaning of the work isn’t clear - it’s oepn to interpretation.</li>
  <li>An <strong>intimate</strong> painting shows private moments in someone’s life.</li>
  <li>intimate: closely acquinted, familiar, close. (as noun: a very close friend)</li>
  <li>The main character has his back to the viewer, which creates a feeling of mystery.</li>
  <li>He <strong>looks as if</strong> he’s thinking about killing himself.(as if + sentence)</li>
  <li>He is <strong>obviously</strong> a sad and lonely man.</li>
  <li>He <strong>seems to</strong> be the most important thing in the painting. Ex: The car <strong>seems to</strong> be running well. Everyone <strong>seems to</strong> have thought the same thing. He <strong>seems to</strong> know the facts. This house <strong>seems to</strong> be empty. He <strong>seems to</strong> be losing. She <strong>seems to</strong> be sad. That <strong>seems to</strong> be the hardest word I’ve learned. It <strong>seems to</strong> be working, though I don’t know for sure. It <strong>seems to</strong> be good. What <strong>seems to</strong> be the problem here? She <strong>seems to</strong> be losing her mind.</li>
  <li>He <strong>appears to</strong> be looking for something better than what he was.</li>
  <li>He looks very proud. I get the impression he feels very pleased with himself.</li>
  <li>He <strong>looks like</strong> a very wealthy man.</li>
  <li>It must be someone in Europe. It <strong>could well</strong> be France.</li>
  <li>Who do you think people in there might be?</li>
  <li>How do you think they’re feeling?</li>
  <li>What might the connection between the two works be?</li>
  <li>In what way are two paintings connected?</li>
  <li>In what way might the viewer’s first impression of the paintings be wrong?</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="sentences-1">Sentences</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Follow me <strong>through into</strong> the next room.</li>
  <li>He died <strong>at the age of 37</strong>, <strong>at a time</strong> when his career was going well and since then he has been forgotten, which <strong>seems to a bit of a shame</strong>, to be honest.</li>
  <li>These two paintings were meant to be hung together as <strong>companion</strong> pieces.</li>
  <li>companion: a person or animal with whom one spends a lot time with whom one travels</li>
  <li>He was <strong>composing</strong> the letter.</li>
  <li>compose: write or create (a work of art, especially music or poetry).Prepare (a text) for printing by manually, mechancally or electronically setting up the letters and other characters in order to be printed.</li>
  <li>She is <strong>digesting</strong> it.</li>
  <li>digest: break down (food) in the alimentary canal into substances that can be absorbed and used by the body.(sindirmek)</li>
  <li>His surroundings create the impression that he’s well travelled.</li>
  <li>He’s man of the world.</li>
  <li>Woman seems to belong more to the domestic world. She looks calm and <strong>content</strong> as she reads.</li>
  <li>content: a state of peaceful happiness</li>
  <li>However, not everything is as it first appears. <strong>Beneath</strong> the surface of the calm domestic world lies trouble.</li>
  <li>beneath: at a lower level or layer than</li>
  <li>Obviously, the woman was so excited to receive her letter that she jumped up in the middle of her needleworkk.</li>
  <li>This <strong>could well</strong> be a symbol of the difficult, stormy nature of love, especially when partners are seperated. There is another letter to deliver, <strong>presumably</strong> to the man.</li>
  <li>Even he, <strong>depicted</strong> in darker, more subtle shades, is a victim of the fires of the heart. The rich red of carpet and the bright <strong>light pouring</strong> in through the window suggest he has a <strong>heated mind</strong>.(angry and excited)</li>
  <li>depict: show or represent by a drawing, painting, or other art form</li>
  <li>The underlying message now seems <strong>painfully clear</strong>: passion can lead to chaos.</li>
  <li>painfully clear: it is embrassing because it is so clear/obvious</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="Study notes" /><category term="Blog-writing" /><category term="Open-source" /><category term="Notes" /><category term="English" /><category term="Entertainment" /><category term="Habits" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notes from English study about describing]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Notes-1: English study about entertainment</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/study%20notes/Notes-1-English/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Notes-1: English study about entertainment" /><published>2022-03-11T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-03-11T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/study%20notes/Notes-1-English</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/study%20notes/Notes-1-English/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) Notes-1: English study about entertainment</p>

<h3 id="questions">Questions:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Where do you think the place is?</li>
  <li>Would you want to read in a place like this?</li>
  <li>Do you usually take a book with you when you’re travelling or do you prefer e-book readers?</li>
  <li>What’s the nicest or most unusual place that you’ve spent time reading in?</li>
  <li>Do you read much?</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="example-answers">Example answers:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>I like all kinds of stuff as well -rock, pop, even some classical.</li>
  <li>I don’t tend to during the week, though, because I’ve got to get up early and basically my parents prefer me to stay at home.</li>
  <li>Not as much as I’d like to, because I really love it - especially musicals. The seats are so expensive I can’t afford to go more than a couple  of times a year.</li>
  <li>I find it a bit boring. It’s not really my kind of thing and I’m not very good at it either.</li>
  <li>Probably less than I think I do. It’s always on in the background, you know, but I don’t pay much attention to it most of the time.</li>
  <li>I will watch a big game if there2s one on and the occasional film, but apart from that, most of it’s rubbish.</li>
  <li>Yeah, I guess so. I generally cycle to college as well -unless it’s raining.</li>
  <li>I tend to watch films on demand through my TV at home.</li>
  <li>Not as much as I used to.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="vocab">Vocab:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Now and again   -   ?</li>
  <li>Tend to     -</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="habits-grammer">Habit’s Grammer</h3>
<ul>
  <li>
    <h2 id="past">Past:</h2>
  </li>
  <li>To talk about past habits, we can use the past simple, used to + infinitive(without to) or would + infinitive(without to). Examples:</li>
  <li>I listened to music all the time when I was younger.</li>
  <li>I used to listen music all the time when I was younger.</li>
  <li>I’d listen to music all the time when I was younger.</li>
  <li>
    <h2 id="present">Present:</h2>
  </li>
  <li>To talk about current habits we can use the present simple, tend to + infinitive(without to) and will + infinitive(without to)</li>
  <li>I listen to music all the time.</li>
  <li>I tend to watch films on demand through my TV.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="adverbs-and-adverbal-phrases-for-frequency">Adverbs and adverbal phrases for frequency:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>always, all the time, constantly</li>
  <li>normally, usually, as a rule, one the whole, by and large</li>
  <li>sometimes, now and again, once in a while</li>
  <li>almost never, very rarely, hardly ever, once in a blue moon</li>
  <li>not as much as  + I’d like to / I want / I used to / I did before</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="making-negatives-for-habits">Making negatives for habits</h3>
<ul>
  <li>We can make negatives with tend to and used to in different ways.</li>
  <li>I didn’t use to like it very much.</li>
  <li>I never used to listen to music at home.</li>
  <li>I tend not to go to the cinema that much.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="mistakes">Mistakes:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Don’t say <em>use to</em> or <em>used to</em> to talk about habits in the present. Ex:
    <ul>
      <li>I (<del>use to</del>) <strong>usually</strong> / <strong>tend to</strong> go out with friends on a Friday.</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>Don’t use the past continuous to talk about past habits. Ex:
    <ul>
      <li>I (<del>was going</del>) <strong>went</strong> / <strong>used to go</strong> swimming a lot when I was younger.</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>Don’t use <em>would</em> to talk about character and other kinds of states. Ex:
    <ul>
      <li>I (<del>would have</del>) <strong>had</strong> / <strong>used to have</strong> long hair when I was younger.</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>Don’t use <em>how</em> instead of as in comparatives. Ex:
    <ul>
      <li>I don’t go as much (<del>how</del>) <strong>as</strong> I’d like to.</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>

<h3 id="did-you-know">Did you know?</h3>
<ul>
  <li><em>Would</em> is actually far more common than <em>used to</em> to talk about past habits. That’s because while we often introduce a topic with <em>used to</em>, we tend to give details with <em>would</em>. Ex:
    <ul>
      <li>I <strong>used to make</strong> my own films when I was younger. <strong>I’d watch</strong> famous films and get ideas and then my brother and I <strong>would try</strong> to make our own versions. <strong>We’d then do</strong> screenings for our family.</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>

<h3 id="ex">Ex:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>By and large, I don’t tend to watch TV much. There are too many ads, which annoys me.</li>
  <li>I don’t see her as much as I used to, because we’re both so busy.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="Study notes" /><category term="Blog" /><category term="Open-source" /><category term="Notes" /><category term="English" /><category term="Entertainment" /><category term="Habits" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notes from English study about entertainment]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Homework: A article about an small and old town</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/article/Golden-halfmoon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Homework: A article about an small and old town" /><published>2022-03-09T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-03-09T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/article/Golden%20halfmoon</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/article/Golden-halfmoon/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) Town homework</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>The town we will talk about is Halfeti. It is part of the city named Sanliurfa which is famous for being the source of religion in the world. In my country, we call this city the city of prophets. Because lots of prophets have been there during history, like Muse, Abraham, Elyasa, Adem, Ayub. And also a temple named Göbeklitepe dates back to 9500 BC. During endless stream of time, the city managed to survive in mandatory of different countries. In this matter, the town Halfeti has a unique position in one respect. It has a castle in the middle of the river which were defining the border of the Eastern Roman Empire. When you see the picture of the castle you see how fairly reasonable to build it there. It is like the wall in the game of thrones. Because the river still defines the east in Turkey. If you want to pass the west side you should pass across the river. Besides, according to the book Homo Sapiens, the River Euphrates defines the Fertile Crescent with another river named Tigris. The region around these two rivers was very productive and important during history so the agriculture, religion, and writing were sourced from Fertile Crescent. Nowadays, the situation is slightly different. Rivers are still very important but industries were not established there. Despite being so historic they don’t have enough amenities. In Halfeti people has a living just from agriculture. The discovery of the first temple of the world in Urfa started to attract tourists. Moreover, having a sub-merged town under the river makes the Halfeti attractive for tourists. Some parts are photogenic but it was a ghost town when I was a child. Nowadays, it is a lively town with sailing, canoe, and diving amenities. There are not many residents and no imposing buildings. Also, because of the narrow streets, I suggest that to leave your car on the main road and walk. Because it is a Cita Slow with a gentle rhythm and a self-contained environment.</p>
</blockquote>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="Article" /><category term="Blog" /><category term="Open-source" /><category term="Article" /><category term="Towns" /><category term="Halfeti" /><category term="Sanliurfa" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A writing example for a small and old town]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Story: The middle men and old man</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/story/The-middle-man/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Story: The middle men and old man" /><published>2022-03-06T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-03-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/story/The%20middle%20man</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/story/The-middle-man/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) Middle men and old man</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>There was a man with a pencil in the middle. Middle of what? Who knows? He always felt like this without any idea for reason. He was brought up in a conservative family that potentially was in the heart of his life. But he doesn’t want to remember those days anymore. He knows how he felt after expelling from school and being like on the ledge of family. His father was like a sheer wall for every discussion and preventing him to shape his own way. Maybe that was because of buzzing news about war and the bad economy, but there should have been more. He has never known that. Because, after staying in the zone and hard working he got the foot in the door of university and left them behind. He hasn’t looked back after this moment and flashed around the country with his exam scores. Everyone was stunned because it was impossible to work flawlessly in that conditions. It was merely a small possibility to rally after this long period of indolence life. But they had forgotten how greasy he is for his decisions and after deciding to his way how hard to change his mind. Now he was at the summit of Mont Blanc and has just signed the summit book. He was standing on his planted steps with an old feeling like being in the middle of a low surrounding.
(<em>by listening blues</em>)</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>There was a man with a pencil in the middle of foreigners. They had come from far but he was from the city. Unlike others, he felt fatigued in the middle of the way but he rallied by staying in the zone and pushing towards his limits. In the end, these bad feelings turned into being stunned due to the accomplishment of this goal. Because it was a merely impossible dream for someone at that age. After he explained his decision, all family members warned him about how this event potentially can kill him. They said that he was in the heart of the family and he shouldn’t do that. However, it was not true and he has felt like he is on the ledge of the family until this moment. Now he was standing over planted steps in the summit. This was the point he got his foot in the door of climbing and became the oldest person who climbed to Mont Blanc. The news was buzzing this journey and it flashed around the world.
(<em>by listening blues</em>)</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>The old man was fainted due to lack of sleep and fatigue. Because he had already been sick. Writing and staying in the zone for several hours was potentially dangerous. The doctor and all family members warned him but after getting his foot in the door of writing he became more undeterred and it was impossible to dissuade him. He was a famous writer and had flashed around the world once upon a time. So, even getting stuck in some points he rallied to finish this book before the party. The book was supposed to be a birthday gift the next day. There was merely a small time before the party and the book was finally completed. Everything was working flawlessly according to his plan. The girl would be stunned when she saw the book had written for her. The old man closed the book and named it by using one of the greasy tags. He wasn’t aware of the broken door ledge and also that the name will have been buzzing in the news the next day. Because it was the last book of a great writer who was at the summit of his career. During his long and successful journey, he hasn’t looked back but it was time to rest last time. By this book, an old saying is brought up again. There is no reward without taking risks.
(<em>by listening rock</em>)</p>
</blockquote>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="Story" /><category term="Blog" /><category term="Open-source" /><category term="Story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A story about the middle men and old man]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to contribute</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/how-to-blogging/How-to-contribute-copy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to contribute" /><published>2022-02-19T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-02-19T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/how-to-blogging/How%20to%20contribute%20copy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/how-to-blogging/How-to-contribute-copy/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) How to contribute</p>

<p>To create post you can add a new <strong><em>.md</em></strong> file in <strong><em>posts</em></strong> folder and create a pull request for your contribution. The name of file should start with the date and should contaion title with in the format <strong><em>yyyy-mm-dd-Title of content</em></strong>.<br />
You also need to set the features for file in header of file. They are</p>
<ul>
  <li>title</li>
  <li>description</li>
  <li>modified(the date)</li>
  <li>tags</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="How-to-blogging" /><category term="Blog" /><category term="Open-source" /><category term="Contributing" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explaniton about how to contribute to this blog]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Embedded readings</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/how-to-embedded/Embedded-readings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Embedded readings" /><published>2020-05-12T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-05-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/how-to-embedded/Embedded%20readings</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/how-to-embedded/Embedded-readings/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) Sources for readings about embedded systems</p>

<p>https://embeddedgurus.com/</p>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="How-to-embedded" /><category term="Embedded" /><category term="Reading" /><category term="Passages" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The list of reading passges about Embedded]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Useful readings for health</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/health/Okumalar-Sa%C4%9Fl%C4%B1k/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Useful readings for health" /><published>2020-05-12T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-05-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/health/Okumalar-Sa%C4%9Fl%C4%B1k</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/health/Okumalar-Sa%C4%9Fl%C4%B1k/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) Useful readings for health</p>

<ul>
  <li>https://www.sencard.com.tr/sen-programi/sen/saglikli-beslenme/saglikli-ve-zararli-yaglar</li>
  <li>https://www.medicalpark.com.tr/ldl-kolesterol/hg-2189</li>
</ul>

<hr />
<p>(<em>Tr</em>) Sağlık üzerine okuma önerileri</p>

<ul>
  <li>https://www.sencard.com.tr/sen-programi/sen/saglikli-beslenme/saglikli-ve-zararli-yaglar</li>
  <li>https://www.medicalpark.com.tr/ldl-kolesterol/hg-2189</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="Health" /><category term="Health" /><category term="Reading" /><category term="Sources" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The list of reading passges about health]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sources for readings about wdt</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/how-to-embedded/WDT-docs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sources for readings about wdt" /><published>2020-05-11T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-05-11T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/how-to-embedded/%20WDT%20docs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/how-to-embedded/WDT-docs/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) Sources for readings about wdt</p>

<p>https://barrgroup.com/embedded-systems/how-to/advanced-watchdog-timer-tips</p>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="How-to-embedded" /><category term="WDT" /><category term="Reading" /><category term="Passages" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The list of reading passages about WDT]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Useful Links</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/links/links/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Useful Links" /><published>2019-12-22T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-12-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/links/links</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/links/links/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) Some useful links</p>

<p>http://pointerpointer.com/ <br />
http://mynoise.net/ <br />
http://draw.io/ <br />
http://wetransfer.com/ <br />
http://radio.garden/ <br />
http://gutenberg.org/ <br />
http://librivox.org/ <br />
http://freerice.com/ <br />
http://outline.com/ <br />
https://www.howmanypeopleareinspacerightnow.com/ <br />
https://haveibeenpwned.com/ <br />
https://geoguessr.com/ <br />
https://rave.dj/ <br />
https://temp-mail.org/</p>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="Links" /><category term="Interesting-websites" /><category term="Useful-links" /><category term="Useful-websites" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[liks can be useful]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Podcast list</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/podcast/Podcasts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Podcast list" /><published>2019-11-26T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-11-26T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/podcast/Podcasts</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/podcast/Podcasts/"><![CDATA[<p>(<em>Eng</em>) List of the best podcasts</p>

<p>Every Day Grammer TV - Voice of America <br />
Monday Morning Podcast <br />
The Smartest Man In The World<br />
Wait Wait… Don’t Tell Me!<br />
Myths and Legends<br />
Phlilosophy Bites<br />
A History of The World in 100 Objects<br />
The Story Collider<br />
The Moth<br />
Intelligence Squared<br />
Story of the Day : NPR<br />
Serial<br />
Flash Forward<br />
This American Life<br />
Rationally Speaking<br />
Brain Matters<br />
Science Friday<br />
Reply All<br />
TED Radio Hour<br />
Surprisingly Awesome<br />
Stuff You Should Know<br />
Freakonomics Radio<br />
Working<br />
How to be Awesome at Your Job<br />
Acquired<br />
That Creative Life<br />
Discovery<br />
99% Invisible<br />
Invisibilia<br />
Radiolab<br />
Money For the Rest of Us<br />
Death, Sex and Money<br />
You Are Not So Smart<br />
TED Talks Daily Audio Selection<br />
Geekstra<br />
Gayrisafi Fikirler<br />
SBS World News Radio<br />
Şapka Altı Konuşmaları<br />
Mücadele<br />
Arka Fon Hikayeleri<br />
Luke’s English Podcast - Learn British with Luke<br />
Ten Questions ESL Podcast<br />
Just Vocabulary | ESL Podcast for Learning SAT and GRE Vocabulary<br />
Happy English Podcsat<br />
podcastinenglish<br />
Espresso English Podcast<br />
Go Nautral English Podcast | Listening &amp; Speaking Lessons<br />
Learn English Through Listening <br />
Culips English Podcast<br />
Better at English - Free English conversation lessons podcast<br />
Satır Arası<br />
Paraşüt’le Üretim Bandı<br />
Radyo 521<br />
Gerisi Hikaye Korku Konuşmaları<br />
Hayatlar Hikayeler<br />
Splendid Speaking<br />
Comedy of The Week<br />
World Book Club<br />
Great Lives<br />
Learning English News Rewiews<br />
6 Minute Grammer<br />
Friday Night Comedy from BBC Radio 4<br />
Sesli Kitap<br />
Embedded System Podcast<br />
Mastering Embedded Systems<br />
Advantech Embedded - IOT Europa<br />
Software Engineering Radio - The Podcast for Professionals<br />
Günün ve Güncelin Edebiyatı<br />
Kodpod<br />
In Our Time : Philosophy<br />
Codefiction Podcast<br />
Words and Their Stories - Voice of America<br />
Haluk Tatar - Yol Sohbetleri<br />
İngilizce Sohbeti<br />
Barış Özcan<br />
Akimboo: A Podcast from Seth Godin<br />
Weekly Dev Tips<br />
WSJ’s The Future of Everything<br />
Disik Didik Freud<br />
Sosyal Psikolojiden Sevgilerle<br />
Hidden Brain<br />
Editor’s picks from the Economist<br />
Haftalık Gündem Değerlendirmesi<br />
Metro FM - Aragaz<br />
Planet Money<br />
Açık Bilim Podcast<br />
All Ears English Podcast<br />
The English We Speak<br />
Bunu Ben De Yaparım<br />
6 Minute Vocabulary<br />
İlk Sayfası<br />
Fularsız Entellik<br />
6 Minute English<br />
Psikolog Beyhan Budak<br />
İngilizce Saati<br />
Virgin Radio - Mesut Süre ile Rabarba</p>]]></content><author><name>ilhan</name></author><category term="Podcast" /><category term="Podcasts" /><category term="Podcasts-for-English" /><category term="Podcasts-in-English" /><category term="Podcast-in-Turkish" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The list of the podcasts I like to listen]]></summary></entry></feed>